麻烦递一下黄芥末
Would you pass the mustard?
好
Sure.
想听一个有关黄芥末的有趣知识吗
Hey, want to hear a fun fact about mustard?
黄芥末主要味道来源的芥子油甙
Is it that the glucosinolates which give mustard its flavor
是白菜花科植物为了
were evolved by the cabbage family
抵御毛毛虫而进化形成的吗
as a chemical defense against caterpillars?
是的
Yeah.
挺有意思
Well, that was fun.
不错哦  莱纳德
Good for you, Leonard.
你们好啊
Hey, there.
你们早到了
Hey, you're early.
电影还有一个小时才开始呢
The movie doesn't start for an hour.
其实我们不去看电影了
Actually, we're not going to the movies.
我们是来绑架你的
We are here to kidnap you.
你们说什么呢
What are you talking about?
你跟佩妮私定终身
Well, you eloped and we didn't get a chance
我们没机会给你办单身汉派对
to throw you a bachelor party,
所以现在楼下有一台面包车
so there's a van downstairs
而我们上来要押你去
and we're here to take you
一个神秘地点过周末
to a surprise location for the weekend.
这算哪门子绑架
Well, I'd hardly call this kidnapping.
眼罩呢
Where's the blindfold?
封嘴的胶布呢
Where's the duct tape?
给我打电话要求付赎金
Where's the part where you call me and demand ransom
然后我试图拖延通话时间
and I try to keep you on the phone,
你们却在定位成功的前几秒挂了
but you hang up seconds before I can trace it
让我说出"我太老了  力不从心了"的桥段呢
and then I say, "I'm getting too old for this crud"?
我们什么时候能走人
When do we leave?
现在
Right now.
佩妮给你打包好行李了
Yeah, Penny packed you a bag.
走起
Wow, okay.
你真的要上一台面包车
You're seriously going to get in a van
让这俩家伙带你到神秘地点
and let these two take you to an unknown destination
一整个周末吗
for an entire weekend?
不只是他  你也得来
Oh, not just him; you're coming, too.
你凭啥觉得我会乖乖配合
Oh, and how do you think you're going to get me to do that?
放开我
Unhand me!
这太扯了
This is ridiculous!
我说了让你用胶带封住他的嘴
I told you to put tape on his mouth!
我也说了这货咬我
And I told you he bit me!
翻译：赛太公一脚踹飞  YY猫满地找牙
猫王也在帮忙找  别扭大菜
我被人强押上车已经够惨了
It's bad enough I'm being taken against my will.
为什么这车还偏偏是
I don't see why it has to be in
某个嬉皮士的移动炮房
some hippie's mobile sex dungeon.
谢尔顿  这台车另有玄机哦
Well, Sheldon, there's something about this van
你绝对会很感兴趣
that you're going to find very interesting.
它是以梅毒为动力的吗
It runs on syphilis?
这台车的主人曾是你
This van was owned and driven by your personal
物理界的偶像
physics hero...
理查德·费曼
Richard Feynman.
美国物理学家  1965年获诺贝尔物理奖
曾被评选为有史以来最伟大的物理学家之一
-不可能  -是真的
- No. - Yeah!
我一个朋友借我开的
A buddy of mine let me borrow it.
这曾是费曼的车吗
This was Feynman's van?
太酷了
That's so cool.
而且还维持着他开它时的原貌呢
Yeah, nothing's been changed since he drove it.
我猜他用这台屌车泡过不少可爱研究生
I bet he picked up a lot of cute grad students in this bad boy.
还在车上跟她们聊了物理
Yeah, and talked about physics with them!
能给个目的地的提示吗
So, are you gonna give us a clue where we're headed?
行  我想想啊
Uh, okay, let's see...
那里有辣的食物
They've got spicy food
而且你有可能会腹泻
and there's a chance you'll get diarrhea.
印度
India.
那地方开车能到
We can drive there.
你家吗
Your house?
我们要去墨喜哥啦
We are going to Meh-he-co!
我从来没去过那里呢
Fun, I've never been there!
莱纳德  别被他们骗了
Leonard, don't be fooled!
我是德州人
I'm from Texas--
墨喜哥是西语的墨西哥
Meh-he-co is Spanish for Mexico.
墨西哥哪里不好
What's wrong with Mexico?
烦人墨西哥街头乐队  野狗
Uh, mariachi bands, wild dogs,
因为里面有虫  而能跳动的墨西哥跳豆
beans that jump around 'cause there's a worm inside.
冷静好吗
Okay, calm down.
这周末有个主题
There's a theme to this weekend.
我们要开着费曼的车去墨西哥
We are going to Mexico in Feynman's van
还要住在费曼用诺贝尔奖奖金
to stay at the vacation house Feynman bought
买下来的度假别墅
with the money from his Nobel Prize.
泄停封万岁
Viva la Imodium!
去嘛  莱纳德去过单身汉派对
Come on, Leonard's doing bachelor stuff.
你确定不要我们带你去牛郎舞厅吗
You sure we can't take you to a strip club?
不用了  如果我想要看赤裸舞男
Nah, if I want to see a naked dancing man,
等莱纳德洗澡时去冲马桶  就能吓得他乱蹦
I just flush the toilet while Leonard's in the shower.
我知道我们没有要大肆庆祝
I know we're not making a fuss,
但本着单身女郎派对的精神
but in the spirit of bachelorette parties,
我做了男人性器官形状的饼干
I made cookies in the shape of male genitals.
你不用那么麻烦...
You really didn't have to...
1:1真鸡模型啊
That is anatomic.
谢谢
Thank you.
静脉是用条状软糖做的
The veins are gummy worms.
瞧
Oh, look,
犹太[割包皮]与非犹太
Jewish and gentile.
面团多了
I had extra dough.
是莱纳德
Oh, that's Leonard.
他说马上要过边境了
He said they're about to cross the border.
希望男生们在墨西哥不会玩太疯
I hope the boys don't get too crazy in Mexico.
是啊  大家快锁好家里女儿
Oh, yeah, right. Lock up your daughters
否则淫贼谢尔顿
or Sheldon might lecture them
会教育她们有关北美自由贸易协议的事
about the North American Free Trade Agreement.
要命  那晚真是漫长啊
Boy, that was a long night for me.
根据这个墨西哥海关网站
According to this Mexican Customs Web site,
游客们不许携带超过五片激光光盘
visitors may not bring more than five laser discs,
二十片光盘
20 compact discs
或十二张录影带
or 12 VHS tapes.
我们没有带那些东西
We don't have any of those.
你怎么能确定
How can you be sure?
费曼开这台车的年代  录影带称霸天下
VHS was king when Feynman drove this van.
说不定这车上哪里有暗格
For all we know, there are hidden compartments
藏满了健美皇后简·方达的健身影带
lousy with Jane Fonda workout videos.
如果这车上有暗格
If there was a hidden compartment,
你不觉得你早就被塞进去了吗
don't you think you'd be stuffed in it by now?
大家的黄热病疫苗还没过期吧
Are we all up to date on our yellow fever inoculations?
去墨西哥不需要接种黄热病疫苗
You don't need a yellow fever shot to go to Mexico.
小心驶得万年船
You can never be too careful.
我去年去未来世界主题公园时就打了一针
I got one last year before I went to Epcot.
佩妮  婚后生活如何
So, Penny, how's married life?
还不错啊
Oh, it's good.
现在就希望莱纳德能鼓起勇气
I just wish Leonard would work up the courage
告诉谢尔顿他要搬来跟我住
to tell Sheldon he's moving in here.
你们俩还没住在一起吗
You guys still aren't living together?
住一起啊  但谢尔顿也睡这
We are. I mean, he sleeps here.
但说不准哪天
But it's only a matter of time
谢尔顿做了恶梦
before Sheldon has a bad dream
会抱着他的莱纳德人形抱枕爬上我们的床
and tries to climb into bed with the Leonard-shaped pile of pillows.
说到谢尔顿
Speaking of Sheldon,
你的单身生活又如何
how's single life treating you?
还行吧
Fine, I guess.
我就专注在自己身上
I've been focusing on me.
我之前还在想要不要换下穿衣风格
I was thinking about changing my wardrobe.
-当然  -好样的
- Yes! - Good for you!
但我后来决定我才不要因为某个男人
But then I decided I don't want to go changing who I am
改变原本的自己
just because of some man.
-当然  -好样的
- Yes. - Good for you.
很多人
You know, it is normal
在分手之后都会想改头换面
to want to change your look after a breakup.
其实我在考虑做一个小小的改变
Actually, I was thinking of making one small change.
-换毛衣  -换眼镜
- Your sweater? - Your glasses?
-换发型  -换鞋子
- Your hair? - Your shoes!
穿耳洞
Piercing my ears.
你以前从来没穿过吗
You really never had that done?
我妈说穿耳洞的人不是妓女
My mom said pierced ears were for whores,
就是海盗和妖怪
pirates and genies.
好吧  你现在都是大人了
Okay, well, you're a grown woman now.
我知道  但谢尔顿在
I know, but Sheldon had this clause
《恋爱协议》里
in the Relationship Agreement
明文禁止做美容手术
forbidding cosmetic surgery
除非做出来效果像克林贡人
unless it's to look like a Klingon.
我们带你去商场里做就好啦
We'll take you to the mall to get it done.
干嘛  我在这就能帮她做
Why? I can do it right here.
是吗
Really?
-你有打耳洞的枪吗  -没有
- You have a piercing gun? - No.
用一根针和一颗冰块就能搞定
All you need is a needle and an ice cube.
我以前做过很多次啦
I've done it, like, a dozen times.
这样好吗
Oh, I don't know.
来嘛  我会很温柔的
Oh, come on. I'll be gentle.
让我来破你耳朵的处吧
Let me take your ear virginity.
这个派对感觉好奇怪
This party's weird.
别开这么快
Hey, watch your speed.
听说墨西哥警察专找游客麻烦
I hear the Mexican police target tourists.
别担心啦
Oh, not a problem.
如果发生什么事
If anything goes down,
我们就让库萨帕里坐到驾驶座上
we just put Koothrappali in the driver's seat
再给他弄顶墨西哥草帽戴上
and slap a sombrero on his head.
伙计  你一口气能激怒多少个种族
Dude, how many races can you offend in a single breath?
不晓得  你跟我一起看过奥林匹克运动会吗
I don't know. Have you watched the Olympics with me?
谢尔顿  你能相信我们开的这辆面包车
Sheldon, can you believe that we're driving in a van that was owned by
曾属于20世纪最伟大的科学家之一吗
one of the greatest scientific minds of the 20th century?
简直就像蝙蝠战车
It's like the Batmobile.
前提是蝙蝠侠真实存在
If Batman was real
而且是一位物理学家
and a physicist
车还得不酷才行
and his car wasn't cool.
这体验的确非比寻常
It is extraordinary.
或许这车能让我们沾上他的好运呢
Perhaps some of his mojo will rub off on us.
或许蹭蹭他的车和豪宅
Maybe between this and his beach house,
我们能被激励  成就大事
we will be inspired to greatness.
通常我不会对符咒或护身符寄予厚望
I usually don't put too much stock in charms and talismans.
然而我必须承认
However, even I must admit
自己的屁股坐在
feeling Richard Feynman's butt dent
理查德·费曼的屁股印上
cupping my own bottom...
真是让我创意如泉涌啊
that does get the creative juices flowing.
这车我还得还回去呢
Hey, I have to return this van.
麻烦不要让你的创意"喷射"出你的裤子
Keep your creative juices in your pants.
怎么回事
What was that?
可能爆胎了
I think it's a tire.
没准是土匪朝咱们开枪了
What if it's banditos shooting at us?
没准我们会被绑架
What if we get kidnapped?
没准我们余生会沦落到某个工厂
What if we end up in a factory making Bart Simpson pinatas
终日做卡通皮纳塔
for the rest of our lives?!
一种纸糊的容器  里面装满糖果与玩具
在节庆或生日是挂空中  让人击打
爆胎而已啦
It's the tire.
莱纳德
Leonard?
干嘛
What?
我太老了  力不从心了
I am getting too old for this crud.
艾米  我注意到你脸书的状态
Amy, I noticed your status still says
还是"恋爱中"
"In a relationship" on Facebook.
你说得对
You're right.
我应该通知我脸书上所有的朋友
I should probably let all of my Facebook friends know.
佩妮  我已经分手了
Penny, I'm no longer in a relationship.
你的状态改为"已婚"了吗
Did you change yours to "Married" yet?
还没
Uh, no, not yet.
有几个人我还没亲自告诉他们
There's still a few people I haven't told personally.
谁
Who?
就我爸妈
Oh, just my parents
和我全家人
and my entire family.
-什么  -为什么
- What? - Why?
我不想让我爸伤心
Well, I don't want to hurt my dad.
他一直梦想着
You know, he always wanted
在自己女儿的婚礼上跟她共舞
to dance with his daughter at her wedding.
那你姐姐的婚礼呢
What about your sister's wedding?
没跳两下她羊水就破了
They started to, then her water broke.
如果他发现我们私定终身了
You know, if he finds out we eloped,
我爸肯定心碎不已
it's gonna break his heart.
你觉得你能瞒他瞒多久
How long do you think you can keep it from him?
对啊  你瞒得越久不就越坏事吗
Yeah, isn't it gonna get worse the longer you wait?
不一定哦
Well, not necessarily.
我爸一天天在老去
You know, Dad's not getting any younger,
所以等到他年老不记事时
so if I wait long enough,
我就告诉他  当初是他陪我走红毯
I'll just tell him he walked me down the aisle
场面非常感人
and it was magical.
你什么时候学会换轮胎的
When did you learn how to change a tire?
任何一个有自尊心的绅士都应该知道这个
Every self-respecting gentleman should know how
以防哪天在路边遇到有一位
in case he comes across a damsel in distress
需要帮助的少女
by the side of the road.
如果我看见一个蝎子
If I see one scorpion,
我就跳上你们谁的肩膀
I am getting on someone's shoulders
永远都不下来
and never coming down.
你遇到的是需要帮助的少男
And there's your damsel.
这螺母卡得太死了
Wow, this one's really stuck.
你拧对方向了吗
Are you turning it the right way?
不
No.
我顺利拧下其他四个螺母后
I took the other four off
突然一拍脑袋  心想
and when I got to this one, I thought,
"太千篇一律了  换个方向试试吧"
"You know, I'm in a rut. Let's shake things up."
让我试试
Here, let me try.
你说得对  另一个方向也拧不动
You're right, it doesn't turn the other way.
好了  大功告成
There you go. You're all done!
没有想象中那么痛啊
That wasn't so bad.
真好看
Nice.
要是我妈现在看到我
Boy, if my mom could see me now,
她会把我锁进罪恶衣柜
she'd lock me in the sin closet.
你是开玩笑的吧
That's a joke, right?
其实  她才是那个笑话
Actually, the joke was on her.
因为我可以从柜门缝隙之间看到电视
I could still see the TV through the slats.
我开始明白你为啥和你妈不太亲近了
I'm starting to see why you and your mom aren't very close.
我打赌她结婚时还是会通知她妈
Bet she'd still tell her if she got married.
你就是不肯放过我  是吧
You're not gonna let this go, are you?
把他们蒙在鼓里是挺过分的
Well, it's kind of sad that they don't know.
他们多喜欢莱纳德啊
I mean, they love Leonard.
好吧  你们想让我打电话
Fine, you want me to call?
那我就打
I'll call.
我怎么这么紧张啊
Why am I so nervous?
这很正常
It's understandable.
艾米也很怕告诉她妈和谢尔顿分手的事
Amy was afraid to tell her mom she broke up with Sheldon.
是吗  结果怎么样
Yeah? How did it go?
她逼着你爬进分手抽屉吗
Did she make you crawl into the breaking-up drawer?
老实说
Uh, well, actually, to be honest...
我还没告诉她呢
I-I haven't told her yet.
你这么起劲催着我
You've been giving me a hard time
而你自己却还没把分手的事告诉你妈
and you haven't even told your mom about Sheldon?
我失血过多  头好晕哦
I'm feeling a little dizzy from all the blood loss.
我听不懂你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
好吧  我给我家打电话
Fine. I'm calling home,
我打完以后  你给你妈打电话
but when I'm done, you're calling your mother.
你说得倒轻巧
Easy for you to say.
你又不需要这样偷偷摸摸地看《新闻60分》
You never had to watch 60 Minutes like this.
爸爸
Hey, Daddy.
帅妞
Hey, slugger.
你过得好吗
How's my girl?
挺好  我妈在吗
Uh, good. Is mom around?
她带你哥哥出去庆祝了
Ah, she took your brother out to celebrate.
他刚获得了他的第十个"一个月没喝酒"奖章
He just got his tenth one-month sober chip.
她要给他做个奖章小项链
Yeah, she's gonna make him a little necklace.
我待会再打给她
Okay, I'll talk to her later.
爸爸  我有事要告诉你
Uh, Dad, there's something I need to tell you.
我和莱纳德结婚了
Leonard and I got married.
真的吗
You did?
什么时候
When?
上周  对不起  我应该早点告诉你
Last week. I'm sorry, I should've told you.
都怪我们一时冲动
It was a spur of the moment thing.
我觉得很愧疚
I feel terrible.
求求你不要对我失望
Please don't be too disappointed.
你开心吗
Are you happy?
开心呀
Very.
莱纳德是个非常棒的人
Leonard is so great.
那我为你开心
Well, then I'm happy for you.
谢谢你  爸爸
Aw, thank you, Daddy.
这对我来说太重要了
That means so much.
我明白  那些会让人难过的事
Well, I understand it's hard to tell someone something
是挺难说出口的
if you think it's gonna upset 'em.
没错
It is.
你真是世上最好的爸爸
You're the best dad ever.
是啊  先别这么说
Yeah. Uh, hold that thought.
我也有个小事没告诉你
I've been sitting on a little news myself.
什么事
Well, what is it?
你知道我为拖拉机配了个旋转式耕耘机吗
You know that rototiller I got for the tractor?
不知道
No.
你真该来看一看
Oh, you should see it.
这机器太帅了
It is a beautiful piece of machinery.
总之...
Anyway, uh...
我倒车时把你的宠物猪绞进去了
I backed over your pet pig with it.
小月舞吗
Moondance?
是的  他已经没法跳舞了
Yeah, he's, uh, not dancing anymore.
你弄死了我的猪
You killed my pig?
不是我干的
I did not kill him.
是兽医结果了他
The vet took care of that.
什么时候的事
When?
大概10到12个月之前吧
Oh... ten, 12 months ago.
你瞒了一年都不告诉我吗
You didn't tell me for a year?!
哈哈  有其父必有其女  对吧
Well, apple doesn't fall far from the tree, does it?
爱你  帅妞  挂了
Love ya, slugger. Gotta go!
好了艾米  该你了
Okay, Amy, your turn.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
这叫做拉玛泽呼吸法
It's called Lamaze breathing.
有助于帮你使劲
It helps you push.
太好了
Great.
他在使子宫的劲呢
He's pushing with his uterus.
肯定还有更好的办法来拧
There's got to be a smarter way of removing it.
对呀  这不过是个简单的物理问题
Yeah, this is nothing more than a physics problem.
没错
Right.
阿基米德曾经说
Archimedes once said,
"给我一根足够长的杠杆
"Give me a leever long enough
和一个支点
and a fulcrum on which to place it,
我就能撑起地球"
and I shall move the world."
没错
Of course.
我们只需要找到
All we need is to find stuff
一根足够长的杠杆
to make a leever big enough to fix this.
说得对
Exactly.
我想这周围肯定有什么
I'll bet there's something around here
可以用来做杠棍
that could be a lehver.
我想想  杠棍  杠棍
Let's see, a lehver, A lehver...
等一下
Everybody hold on!
我们先一步一步地来解决这个问题
Let's take this problem one step at a time.
首先  我们需要决定
First, we need to decide
到底是叫杠杆  还是杠棍
whether we're calling it leever or lehver.
一旦我们确定了叫杠杆
And the sooner we decide it's leever,
我们就能挽起袖子  而不是舅子
the sooner we can roll up our sleeves-- not slehves--
开始工作了
and get to work.
我们要"允远"留在这鬼地方了
We're gonna be here "Foreever."
我谢谢你们全家啊
Thanks a lot, guys.
关我们什么事
What did we do?
在我打那通电话之前
Before I made that call,
我的猪猪还活着
my pig was alive and happy
欢快地在泥巴里打滚
and rolling around in the mud.
现在他被非法葬在我们家后院
Now he's illegally buried in our backyard
紧挨着我太奶奶
next to my great-grandmother.
真的吗  没有被吃掉
Really? They didn't eat him?
没有
No.
他是我们挚爱的家族成员
He was a beloved member of the family.
早餐肉中的成员吗
The breakfast meat family?
这不好笑
It's not funny.
该你了  给你妈打电话
You're up. Call your mother.
还是等会吧
Oh, maybe later.
猪猪不幸逝世  让我深感悲痛
Your pig dying made me sad.
还有点饿
And a little hungry.
马上打电话
Phone, now.
知道了  好了
Okay. Okay.
好吧
Fine.
喂  妈妈啊
Hi, Mom.
你倒是拨号啊
Try dialing.
被你看穿了呀
You saw that, huh?
妈妈  你好吗
Hi, Mom. How are you doing?
我也好
Oh, good.
工作怎么样
How's work?
挺好的
That's nice.
我很好
I'm fine.
听着  我一直想问
Hey, listen, I've been meaning to ask,
多姨和弗洛伦斯姨怎么一直处不来呢
how come Aunt Doe and Aunt Florence never got along?
给我吧
Okay, just... give me that.
艾米跟谢尔顿分手了
Amy broke up with Sheldon,
她打了耳洞
she got her ears pierced
还非逼我们吃大屌饼干
and she made us eat penis cookies!
等等
Hang on.
她想跟你谈谈
She wants to talk to you.
我感觉杠杆没起作用
I don't think the lever's working.
你凭啥那么说
What makes you say that?
肯定有别的方法可以试试
There's gotta be something else we can try.
这要是在《星际迷航》里
If this was Star Trek,
我们可以用相位枪把它炸开
we could use a phaser to blast it off.
不行  激光束太粗了
No, it's too broad of a beam.
要更精准的
You'd need something more precise,
比如超人的热视线
like Superman's heat vision.
或者绿灯侠的能量戒指
Ooh, the Green Lantern's ring
可以变成大绿手  来拧松它
could make a big green hand that unscrews it.
如果要大绿手
If you need a green hand,
何不直接找绿巨人
why not just use the Hulk?
得了吧
Oh, please,
绿巨人那个脾气哪过得了边防
the Hulk would never get across the border with that temper.
大伙  插一句
Guys, excuse me,
不是说呼叫复仇者联盟的人来
not that calling one of the Avengers
不是完美合理的解决方法
isn't a perfectly reasonable choice,
可我们是科学家
but we're scientists.
不应该用真正的科学去解决吗
Don't you think we can figure this out using actual science?
是的  我们可以运用真正的科学
Yes, we could use science.
但这是你的单身派对
But it's your bachelor party.
高兴点
Lighten up.
科学原理
敲击震荡
* 我们将 *
* We will *
*我们将  敲击震荡你*
* We will percussive shock you *
* 我们将 *
* We will *
*我们将  敲击震荡你*
* We will percussive shock you *
* 伙计  你是个小孩 *
* Buddy you're a boy *
* 在街头吵闹玩耍 *
* Make a big noise playin' in the street
* 一天你将会长大 *
* Gonna be a big man someday *
* 你脸上沾着泥巴  丢人现眼 *
* You got mud on your face, you big disgrace *
* 把问题像铁罐踢来踢去 *
* Kickin' your can all over the place. *
我过目不忘的记忆
I have an eidetic memory.
有时是诅咒般的存在
Sometimes it's a curse.
科学原理
热膨胀
我没想到
I had no idea
墨西哥炸玉米片居然是个好燃料
tortilla chips were such a good fuel source.
基本就是沾满油的纯碳氢化合物
They're basically pure hydrocarbons soaked in fat.
希望轮爪螺母可以膨胀
Let's hope the lug nut expands.
烧食物的香味引来动物怎么办
What if that burning food attracts animals?
我们有很多食物可以给动物吃
We have plenty of food for the animals.
-有吗  -当然
- We do? - Yep.
闪电侠T恤裹着的六尺长香肠
A six-foot wiener in a Flash T-shirt.
一点都不友好
That's not very nice.
这是单身派对   高兴点
It's a bachelor party. Lighten up.
科学原理
加速腐蚀
这难闻的味道是什么
What is that awful smell?
烧着的莎莎酱
It's burning salsa.
希望酸性和盐度与电结合
I'm hoping the acidity and salinity
可以腐蚀部分螺母
combined with electricity will corrode the lug nut off.
多有创意的方法
What an innovative solution.
之前瞧不起你的麻省理工学院学历是我不好
Perhaps I don't give your MIT education enough credit.
我是在谣言终结者上学到的
Yeah, I saw it on Mythbusters.
科学原理
放热反应
好了  这些锈
All right, this rust,
与面包车弄下来的铝
combined with the aluminum recovered from the van,
就是铝热剂了
is now thermite.
很好
Great.
来几小撮就够了
Couple pinches ought to do the trick.
这些够融掉螺母吗
Is that enough to melt the lug nut?
一点点来
Well, let's start small.
可以再加的
We can always add more.
螺母  你确实骁勇善战
You put up a good fight, lug nut,
可惜你遇到对手了[火柴]
but you've met your match.
瞧
Hey, look!
螺母掉了
The lug nut's off.
你们怎么回来了
What are you doing back?
爆胎了
We got a flat
轮胎换不下来
and couldn't get the tire off.
好遗憾
Oh, I'm sorry.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不知道会不会让你们平衡一些
If it makes you feel any better,
我给艾米穿了耳洞
I pierced Amy's ears
她妈妈罚她坐我衣柜里呢
and her mom made her sit in my closet.
我们把费曼先生的面包车烧了
We blew up Feynman's van.
我爸用拖拉机把我的猪猪杀了
My dad killed my pig with his tractor.
我跟谢尔顿在墨西哥共度了一夜
I spent the night in Mexico with Sheldon.
你赢了
You win.